Guide to the Dwight Hall, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, circa 1911-1980; Accession 1988-A-105
  - Boys' Work
    - Reports, 1934-1935 (Box 71, Folder 2295)
    - Working Reserve, 1918 (Box 71, Folder 2296)
  - Brochure (Dwight Hall), 1959 (Box 72, Folder 2297)
  - Brown, W. A., Prof.: Meeting, 1937 (Box 72, Folder 2298)
  - Budget
    - 1968-1969 (Box 72, Folder 2299)
    - Advisory Board (Proposed), 1962-1963 (Box 72, Folder 2300)
    - Committee, 1933-1945 (Box 72, Folder 2301)
  - Budget Drive
    - 1945-1946 (Box 72, Folder 2302)
    - 1949 (Box 72, Folder 2303)
    - 1952 (Box 72, Folder 2304)
    - Records, 1945-1946 (Box 72, Folder 2305)
    - Samples, 1942-1943 (Box 72, Folder 2306)
  - Buildings
    - Furnishings, 1947 (Box 72, Folder 2307)
    - Letters to Henry Chauncey, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 2308)
    - Romodeling Plans: Kitchen, 1956 (Box 72, Folder 2309)
    - South Wing Refurnishing, 1938-1954 (Box 72, Folder 2310)
    - Windows, 1931-1932 (Box 72, Folder 2311)
  - Bulletin
    - 1933 (Box 72, Folder 2312)
    - 1935 (Box 72, Folder 2313)
    - 1935 (Box 72, Folder 2314)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 72, Folder 2315)
    - Board Notices, 1934 (Box 72, Folder 2316)
  - Bureau of Appointments, 1916 (Box 72, Folder 2317)
  - Bursar: Johnson, F. B., 1935-1936 (Box 72, Folder 2318)
  - Bursar: Johnson, F. B., 1937-1938 (Box 72, Folder 2319)
  - Bursar: re Francis Chen, 1938-1939 (Box 72, Folder 2320)
  - Bursary Appointees
    - 1938-1939 (Box 72, Folder 2321)
    - 1942-1943? (Box 72, Folder 2322)
    - 1943 (Box 72, Folder 2323)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 72, Folder 2324)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 72, Folder 2325)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 73, Folder 2326)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 73, Folder 2327)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 73, Folder 2328)
    - 1964-1966 (Box 73, Folder 2329)
  - Buttrick Committee, 1938 (Box 73, Folder 2330)
  - Buttrick Mettings, 1938-1939 (Box 73, Folder 2331)
  - Byers, David, Rev. vitae, 1959-1961 (Box 73, Folder 2332)
  - Byers, O. M. (Rockfeller Foundation), 1960-1963 (Box 73, Folder 2333)
  - Byers Hall, 1930-1931 (Box 73, Folder 2334)
  - Byers Hall: Cabinet, 1928 (Box 73, Folder 2335)
  - Byers Hall: Walter B. Hill, Jr., 1930-1931 (Box 73, Folder 2336)
  - Byrd, William, by Edmund H. Fellowes, 1933? (Box 73, Folder 2337)
  - Cabinet
    - 1919-1920 (Box 73, Folder 2338)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 73, Folder 2339)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 73, Folder 2340)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 73, Folder 2341)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 73, Folder 2342)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 73, Folder 2343)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 73, Folder 2344)
    - 1938-1939 (Box 73, Folder 2345)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 73, Folder 2346)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 73, Folder 2347)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 73, Folder 2348)
    - 1950 (Box 73, Folder 2349)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 73, Folder 2350)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 73, Folder 2351)
    - 1955-1958 (Box 73, Folder 2352)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 74, Folder 2353)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 74, Folder 2354)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 74, Folder 2355)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 74, Folder 2356)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 74, Folder 2357)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 74, Folder 2358)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 74, Folder 2359)
    - 1967 (Box 74, Folder 2360)
    - 1969 (Box 74, Folder 2361)
    - no date (Box 74, Folder 2362)
    - Douglas Carroll, 1931-1937 (Box 74, Folder 2363)
    - Freshman, 1965-1967 (Box 74, Folder 2364)
    - Meeting, 1962-1963 (Box 74, Folder 2365)
    - Miscellaneous, 1961 (Box 74, Folder 2366)
    - Re Liquor in Dwight Hall, 1933-1934 (Box 74, Folder 2367)
    - Sophomore, 1965-1966 (Box 74, Folder 2368)
  - Cadets
    - 1943 (Box 74, Folder 2369)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 74, Folder 2370)
  - Calling Committee
    - 1933 (Box 75, Folder 2371)
    - 1935 (Box 75, Folder 2372)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 75, Folder 2373)
    - Lists, 1934-1935 (Box 75, Folder 2374)
  - Camp Hazen Conference, 1937 (Box 75, Folder 2375)
  - Camp Hazen Conference: Preliminary Data: Batdorf, J. W., 1936-1938 (Box 75, Folder 2376)
  - Camp O-At-Ka
    - 1937 (Box 75, Folder 2377)
    - no date (Box 75, Folder 2378)
    - 1939 (Box 75, Folder 2379)
    - 1940 (Box 75, Folder 2380)
    - 1941 (Box 75, Folder 2381)
    - 1943 (Box 75, Folder 2382)
    - 1949 (Box 75, Folder 2383)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 75, Folder 2384)
  - Campaign for YMCA Work in European Prisoner of War Camps, 1916-1919 (Box 75, Folder 2385)
  - Camps, 1928 (Box 75, Folder 2386)
  - Campbell, Charles S. Memorial, 1955-1958 (Box 75, Folder 2387)
  - Campbell, E. Fay: Sermons, Radio, etcirca, 1941 (Box 75, Folder 2388)
  - Campbell, E. Fay: Trip West, 1939 (Box 75, Folder 2389)
  - Campus Council
    - 1960-1961 (Box 75, Folder 2390)
    - 1961 (Box 75, Folder 2391)
    - 1962 (Box 75, Folder 2392)
    - 1965-1967 (Box 75, Folder 2393)
    - Freshman Material, 1968 (Box 75, Folder 2394)
    - Minutes, 1968 (Box 75, Folder 2395)
  - Campus Sing, 1942 (Box 75, Folder 2396)
  - Canterbury Clubs, 1944 (Box 75, Folder 2397)
  - Capital and Labor, 1930 (Box 75, Folder 2398)
  - Career Conference, 1942 (Box 75, Folder 2399)
  - Caribbean, 1944-1945 (Box 75, Folder 2400)
  - Caribbean, 1945 (Box 75, Folder 2401)
  - Carnegie Music Set, 1937-1938 (Box 75, Folder 2402 - 2403)
  - Cell Group Reports, 1949 (Box 76, Folder 2404)
  - Certification, 1928-1930 (Box 76, Folder 2405)
  - Challenge, 1959-1961 (Box 76, Folder 2406 - 2407)
    - Financial Statements and Budgets, 1959-1961 (Box 76, Folder 2408)
  - Chapel Services, 1940 (Box 76, Folder 2409)
  - Chapel Talks, 1950-1951 (Box 76, Folder 2410)
  - Chapel Talks, Rev. William Sloane Coffin, Jr., 1964 (Box 76, Folder 2411)
  - Chaplain: Denominational Advisory Boards, 1960 (Box 76, Folder 2412)
  - Chaplaincy, 1943-1945 (Box 76, Folder 2413 - 2414)
  - Chaplains, 1961-1977 (Box 76, Folder 2415 - 2416)
  - Chaplains Group, 1959-1960 (Box 76, Folder 2417 - 2419)
  - Chaplains' Loan Fund, 1953-1954 (Box 76, Folder 2420)
  - Charities Drive
    - 1955-1957 (Box 76, Folder 2421)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 76, Folder 2422)
    - 1974-1976 (Box 76, Folder 2423)
    - 1978 (Box 76, Folder 2424)
  - Berkeley, undated (Box 76, Folder 2425)
    - Berkeley College (Raffle Tickets, Winners), 1976-1977 (Box 76, Folder 2426)
    - Berkeley, Welch, undated (Box 76, Folder 2427)
    - Calhoun, undated (Box 76, Folder 2428)
    - Captain's Reports and Recommendations for the 1971 Captain, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 2429)
    - Dance Marathon, 1976-1977 (Box 76, Folder 2430)
    - Davenport (Bernard P. O'Meara), undated (Box 76A, Folder 2431)
    - Durfee Hall, Pierson College, undated (Box 76, Folder 2432)
    - Groshong, Geoffrey, undated (Box 76, Folder 2433)
    - HGS, 22 Woodland St., undated (Box 76, Folder 2434)
    - Jonathan Edwards, Yale Station, Vanderbilt, McClellan, undated (Box 76, Folder 2435)
    - Key Sheets, undated (Box 76, Folder 2436)
    - Law School (Rich Taft), undated (Box 76, Folder 2437)
    - LeBlanc, Donna, undated (Box 76, Folder 2438)
    - McKee, Terry, undated (Box 76, Folder 2439)
    - Medical School, undated (Box 76, Folder 2440)
    - Prize Raffle (Flyers, Prize Lists, Tickets), 1976-1977 (Box 76, Folder 2441)
    - Prize Stuff, 1975-1976 (Box 76, Folder 2442)
    - Prize Stuff, Miscellany, 1975-1976 (Box 76, Folder 2443)
    - Production and Bands, 1976-1977 (Box 76, Folder 2444)
    - Recipient Organizations, 1975-1976 (Box 76, Folder 2445)
    - Saybrook, undated (Box 76, Folder 2446)
    - Stage Lighting Promotions, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 2447)
    - Temple Street, 420, undated (Box 76, Folder 2448)
  - Charter Revision Commission, 1973-1974 (Box 77, Folder 2449)
  - Letter to Henry Chauncey from Sidney Lovett, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 2450)
  - China Colleges, 1944 (Box 77, Folder 2451)
  - China Institute in America, 1945 (Box 77, Folder 2452)
  - China Movement (YMCA), 1942 (Box 77, Folder 2453)
  - China Relief, 1921 (Box 77, Folder 2454)
  - China Relief, 1938 (Box 77, Folder 2455)
  - China: Reports, 1944 (Box 77, Folder 2456)
  - Chinese Christian Conference, 1944-1945 (Box 77, Folder 2457)
  - Chinese Student Christian Association, 1944-1945 (Box 77, Folder 2458)
  - Chinese Students, 1937 (Box 77, Folder 2459)
  - Christ Church, 1943 (Box 77, Folder 2460)
  - Christ Church: Cambridge, 1938-1939 (Box 77, Folder 2461)
  - Christian Association
    - 1955-1956 (Box 77, Folder 2462)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 77, Folder 2463)
    - Adopted Budget, 1963-1964 (Box 77, Folder 2464)
    - Advisory Board (Yale University), 1937-1938 (Box 77, Folder 2465)
    - Graduate Fund: Correspondence of Lawrence R. Wheeler, 1912-1913 (Box 77, Folder 2466)
    - Lists and Proposed Constitution, 1950 (Box 77, Folder 2467)
    - Miscellaneous Memos, 1918 (Box 77, Folder 2468)
    - Newsletters, 1923-1924 (Box 77, Folder 2469)
    - Subscription Correspondences of Lawrence R. Wheeler, 1912-1913 (Box 77, Folder 2470 - 2471)
    - Summer Arts Program, 1975 (Box 77, Folder 2472)
    - Trustee's Meeting, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 2473)
  - Christian Colleges in China, 1938 (Box 77, Folder 2474)
  - Christian Commission (NICC), 1942 (Box 77, Folder 2475)
  - Christian Commission in War Time Campus Missions, 1944 (Box 77, Folder 2476)
  - Christian Community Responsibility Commission, 1944 (Box 77, Folder 2477)
  - Christian Conference
    - 1940 (Box 77, Folder 2478)
    - 1941 (Box 77, Folder 2479)
    - 1941-1942 (Box 78, Folder 2480)
    - 1942 (Box 78, Folder 2481)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 78, Folder 2482)
    - 1944 (Box 78, Folder 2483)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 78, Folder 2484)
  - Christian Evangelism Among Youth, Inc., 1939 (Box 78, Folder 2485)
  - Christian Evangelism for Our Day, 1937 (Box 78, Folder 2486)
  - Christian Fellowship, 1959-1960 (Box 78, Folder 2487 - 2488)
  - Christian Mission
    - 1950-1951 (Box 78, Folder 2489)
    - 1952 (Box 78, Folder 2490)
    - 1953 (Box 78, Folder 2491)
    - 1954 (Box 78, Folder 2492)
    - 1955-1957 (Box 78, Folder 2493)
    - 1959 (Box 78, Folder 2494)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 78, Folder 2495)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 78, Folder 2496)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 78, Folder 2497)
  - Christian World Education Committee, 1931 (Box 78, Folder 2498)
  - Christian World Education Program Council, 1931 (Box 78, Folder 2499)
  - Christianity and Crisis, 1962-1963 (Box 78, Folder 2500)
  - "Christianity at Yale", 1932-1933 (Box 78, Folder 2501)
  - Christmas Festival, 1959 (Box 78, Folder 2502)
  - CHSC, 1972 (Box 78, Folder 2503)
  - Church Committee on Overseas Relief and Reconstruction
    - 1944-1945 (Box 78, Folder 2504)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 78, Folder 2505)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 79, Folder 2506)
  - Church of Christ
    - 1920 (Box 79, Folder 2507)
    - 1943 (Box 79, Folder 2508)
    - 1950 (Box 79, Folder 2509)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 79, Folder 2510)
    - 1955-1957 (Box 79, Folder 2511)
    - 1955-1957 (Box 79, Folder 2512)
    - 1960 (Box 79, Folder 2513)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 79, Folder 2514)
    - 1960-1966 (Box 79, Folder 2515)
    - 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2516)
    - 1963 (Box 79, Folder 2517)
    - 1972 (Box 80, Folder 2518)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 80, Folder 2519)
    - 1959 (Box 80, Folder 2520)
  - Church Relations, 1945-1946 (Box 80, Folder 2521)
  - Church Society for College Work (CSCW), 1945-1946 (Box 80, Folder 2522)
  - Church of Christ Weekly Calendars, 1961-1962 (Box 80, Folder 2523)
  - Church Today, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 2524)
  - Citizens Action Committee (Education Committee), 1956 (Box 80, Folder 2525)
  - City Plan
    - 1974 Jan (Box 80, Folder 2526)
    - 1974 Apr - Jun (Box 80, Folder 2527)
    - 1974 May (Box 80, Folder 2528)
    - 1974 Jun (Box 80, Folder 2529)
    - 1974 Sep (Box 80, Folder 2530)
    - 1974 Oct (Box 80, Folder 2531)
    - 1974 Nov - Dec (Box 80, Folder 2532)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 81, Folder 2533 - 2535)
    - 1975 (Box 81, Folder 2536 - 2537)
  - City Planning, 1969 (Box 81, Folder 2538)
  - "City Problems", 1965-1968 (Box 81, Folder 2539 - 2540)
  - Civil Defense, 1941 (Box 81, Folder 2541)
  - Civil Rights, Address to Foreign Students on, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 2542)
  - Civil Rights: Memoranda and Newsletters, 1964-1965 (Box 81, Folder 2543)
  - Civilian Public Service Unit, 1945 (Box 81, Folder 2544)
  - Clothing Drive, 1960-1966 (Box 81, Folder 2545 - 2546)
  - Class of 1922, Yale College (Box 81, Folder 2547)
  - Class of 1938, 1950 (Box 81, Folder 2548)
  - Class of 1971, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 2549)
  - Coalition for a New University, 1969 (Box 81, Folder 2550)
  - Coeducation, 1970-1973 (Box 81, Folder 2551)
  - Coeducation, 1971 (Box 81, Folder 2552)
  - Coeducation at Yale, undated (Box 82, Folder 2553)
  - Coffin, Henry Sloane Fund, 1945 (Box 82, Folder 2554)
  - Coffin, Henry Sloane Fund (Dinner), 1940 (Box 82, Folder 2555)
  - Coffin, William S., 1975 (Box 82, Folder 2556)
  - Le College Cevenol, 1946 (Box 82, Folder 2557)
  - College Christian Association, undated (Box 82, Folder 2558)
  - College Conference, 1916 (Box 82, Folder 2559)
  - College Directories, 1956-1958 (Box 82, Folder 2560)
  - College Directories, 1961-1962 (Box 82, Folder 2561)
  - College Encounter, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 2562)
  - College Lists, 1944 (Box 82, Folder 2563)
  - College Student Listings, 1974-1976 (Box 82, Folder 2564)
  - College Summer Service Group, 1934 (Box 82, Folder 2565)
  - College Work Study Program, 1971 (Box 82, Folder 2566)
  - Colleges -- Work Being Done in Callepes, 1937-1938 (Box 82, Folder 2567)
  - Colloquy on Christian Leadership, 1949 (Box 82, Folder 2568)
  - Commission on College Work: New England, 1944-1945 (Box 82, Folder 2569)
  - Commission on College Work: New England, 1945-1946 (Box 82, Folder 2570)
  - Commission on the Common Christian Task, 1935-1936 (Box 82, Folder 2571)
  - Commission on Consultations: Central Field (Men), undated (Box 82, Folder 2572)
  - Commission on Message and Purpose, 1930 (Box 82, Folder 2573)
  - Commission on Students and the World Christian Community, 1937 (Box 82, Folder 2574)
  - Commission to Study the Organization of Peace, 1942 (Box 82, Folder 2575)
  - Committees
    - Committee for Christian Colleges in China, 1928 (Box 82, Folder 2576)
    - Committee for Discussion of an Honor System, 1949 (Box 82, Folder 2577)
    - Committee of Seventy-One, 1917 (Box 82, Folder 2578)
    - Committee of Seventy-One, 1917-1918 (Box 83, Folder 2579)
    - Committee of Seventy-One (To Charles S. Campbell), 1917 (Box 83, Folder 2580)
    - Committee of Seventy-One (To Charles S. Campbell, Prohibition Circular), 1917 (Box 83, Folder 2581)
    - Committee of Spiritual Emphasis, undated (Box 83, Folder 2582)
    - Committee of Two Hundred, 1920 (Box 83, Folder 2583)
    - Committee on Bursary Appointments, 1942 (Box 83, Folder 2584)
    - Committee on Friendly Relations Among Foreign Students, 1916 (Box 83, Folder 2585)
    - Committee on Friendly Relations Among Foreign Students, 1944 (Box 83, Folder 2586)
    - Committee on Labor Legislation and Social Reform, 1933 (Box 83, Folder 2587)
    - Committee on Religious Life and Study of University Council, 1960-1961 (Box 83, Folder 2588)
    - Committee on Teaching in the Residential Colleges, 1970's (Box 83, Folder 2589)
    - Committee to Defend America, 1941 (Box 83, Folder 2590)
  - Community Budget Drive, 1949 (Box 83, Folder 2591)
  - Community Charities Drive, 1952 (Box 83, Folder 2592)
  - Community Charities Drive, 1953-1954 (Box 83, Folder 2593)
  - Community Charities Drive, 1959 (Box 83, Folder 2594)
  - Community Council
    - 1930's (Box 83, Folder 2595)
    - 1937-1938 (Box 83, Folder 2596)
    - 1938-1940 (Box 83, Folder 2597)
    - 1940's (Box 83, Folder 2598)
    - 1940 (Box 83, Folder 2599)
    - 1941 (Box 83, Folder 2600)
    - 1943 (Box 83, Folder 2601)
    - 1947 (Box 83, Folder 2602)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 83, Folder 2603)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 83, Folder 2604)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 83, Folder 2605)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 83, Folder 2606)
    - 1955 (Box 83, Folder 2607)
    - 1959 (Box 83, Folder 2608)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 83, Folder 2609)
    - 1960-1962 (Box 83, Folder 2610)
    - 1961 (Box 84, Folder 2611)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 84, Folder 2612)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 84, Folder 2613)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 84, Folder 2614)
    - Annual Reports (Yale), 1938-1941 (Box 84, Folder 2615)
    - Annual Reports (Yale), 1938-1941 (Box 84, Folder 2616)
    - Annual Reports, 1947-1948 (Box 84, Folder 2617)
    - Bills, Board (Yale), 1938-1941 (Box 84, Folder 2618)
    - Chairman, 1968 (Box 84, Folder 2619)
    - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 84, Folder 2620)
    - Minutes, 1968 (Box 84, Folder 2621)
    - Miscellaneous Material, 1939-1940 (Box 84, Folder 2622)
    - New Haven Friends of Boys (Yale), 1947 (Box 84, Folder 2623)
    - Personnel and Progress Reports, 1949 (Box 84, Folder 2624)
    - President's Report (Yale), 1942 (Box 84, Folder 2625)
    - Programs, 1972 (Box 84, Folder 2626)
    - Report for Intercollegiate Council on Community Service (Yale), 1941 (Box 84, Folder 2627)
    - Reports, 1955-1956 (Box 84, Folder 2628)
    - World and Community (Yale), 1947 (Box 84, Folder 2629)
    - World and Community, 1947 (Box 85, Folder 2630)
  - Community Housing and Development Association, 1974-1975 (Box 85, Folder 2631)
  - Community Progress, 1962 (Box 85, Folder 2632)
  - Community Service, 1944-1979 (Box 85, Folder 2633 - 2636)
  - Community Service Center, Barre, MA, 1939 (Box 85, Folder 2637)
  - Community Sings, 1942 (Box 85, Folder 2638)
  - Community Sings, 1942-1943 (Box 85, Folder 2639)
  - Community Sings, 1943 (Box 85, Folder 2640)
  - Concentrated Employment Program: Guidelines for Development and Operations, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 2641)
  - Conference
    - Brook School, 1938 (Box 85, Folder 2642)
    - Connecticut Valley, 1945 (Box 85, Folder 2643)
    - Des Moines, 1919-1920 (Box 85, Folder 2644)
    - Eagles Mere, PA, 1934 (Box 85, Folder 2645)
    - Foreign Mission, 1931 (Box 85, Folder 2646)
    - Jewish-Christian, 1934 (Box 85, Folder 2647)
    - Lisle, 1931 (Box 85, Folder 2648)
    - NY State Student, 1934 (Box 85, Folder 2649)
  - Conference of Yale Christian Communities, 1963-1964 (Box 86, Folder 2650)
  - Conference on Community Service, Harvard, 1941 (Box 86, Folder 2651)
  - Conference on Unemployment in New Haven, 1935 (Box 86, Folder 2652)
  - Conference: Preparatory School, 1927-1928 (Box 86, Folder 2653)
  - Conference Program, 1925 (Box 86, Folder 2654)
  - Conference
    - Silver Bay, N.Y., 1919-1921 (Box 86, Folder 2655 - 2656a)
      General
      Photographs found in Yale University Christian Association minor publications (Yeh 3 +1) and transferred to RU 47 on 15 February 2011.
    - Springfield, 1943 (Box 86, Folder 2657)
    - Student - Faculty, 1930 (Box 86, Folder 2658)
    - Student - Faculty (Detroit), 1930-1931 (Box 86, Folder 2659)
    - Toronto, 1940 (Box 86, Folder 2660)
    - Toronto: Planning Committee, 1939 (Box 86, Folder 2661)
  - Conferences
    - 1916 (Box 86, Folder 2662)
    - 1920 (Box 86, Folder 2663)
    - 1930 (Box 86, Folder 2664)
    - 1932 (Box 86, Folder 2665)
    - 1934 (Box 86, Folder 2666)
    - 1937 (Box 86, Folder 2667)
    - 1938 (Box 86, Folder 2668)
    - 1939 (Box 86, Folder 2669)
    - 1940 (Box 86, Folder 2670)
    - 1943 (Box 86, Folder 2671)
    - 1944 (Box 86, Folder 2672)
    - 1945 (Box 86, Folder 2673)
    - 1946 (Box 86, Folder 2674)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 86, Folder 2675)
    - 1960 (Box 86, Folder 2676)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 86, Folder 2677)
    - 1962 (Box 86, Folder 2678)
    - 1973 (Box 86, Folder 2679)
    - no date (Box 86, Folder 2680)
  - Confirmation Class, 1965-1966 (Box 86, Folder 2681)
  - Congregational, 1945-1961 (Box 86, Folder 2682 - 2683)
  - Congregational Home Missionary Society, 1917 (Box 86, Folder 2684)
  - Congregational Ministers of New Haven, 1925-1926 (Box 86, Folder 2685)
  - Congregational Student Work, 1951 (Box 86, Folder 2686)
  - Congregationalists, Baptists, Catholics (List of), 1921-1922 (Box 86, Folder 2687)
  - Connecticut Chapter, Association of Secretaries, 1940 (Box 86, Folder 2688)
  - Connecticut Citizens' Committee, Incirca, 1939 (Box 86, Folder 2689)
  - Connecticut Council of Churches: 60 Lorraine St., Hartford, CT, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 2690)
  - Connecticut Council of Churches, 1962-1963 (Box 86, Folder 2691)
  - Connecticut Federation of Churches, undated (Box 86, Folder 2692)
  - Connecticut Peace Conference, 1938 (Box 86, Folder 2693)
  - Connecticut Personnel Study, 1927 (Box 86, Folder 2694)
  - Connecticut Temperance Foundation, 1939-1941 (Box 86, Folder 2695)
  - Connecticut United Nations Association, 1944-1945 (Box 86, Folder 2696 - 2697)
  - Connecticut Valley Association of Friends, 1944 (Box 86, Folder 2698)
  - Connecticut Valley Leadership Training Conference, 1943 (Box 86, Folder 2699)
  - Connecticut Valley Presbytery, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 2700)
  - Connecticut Valley Student Missionary Union, 1934-1935 (Box 86, Folder 2701 - 2702)
  - Connecticut YMCA (Box 86, Folder 2703)
    - 1937-1938 (Box 87, Folder 2704)
    - 1943 (Box 87, Folder 2705)
    - 1944 (Box 87, Folder 2706)
    - 1945 (Box 87, Folder 2707)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 87, Folder 2708)
  - Conscientious Objectors, 1940-1942 (Box 87, Folder 2709 - 2710)
  - Constitution Committee, circa 1940's (Box 87, Folder 2711)
  - Constitutions, 1949 (Box 87, Folder 2712)
  - Consumers' League, 1935 (Box 87, Folder 2713)
  - Contribution Correspondence
    - Allen, circa Durand, Yale YMCA General Secretary, 1913-1914 (Box 87, Folder 2714 - 2715)
    - 1920-1921 (Box 87, Folder 2716 - 2717)
  - Contributions
    - 1925 (Box 87, Folder 2718)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 87, Folder 2719)
    - 1929 (Box 87, Folder 2720)
  - Contributors
    - 1937-1940 (Box 87, Folder 2721)
    - 1942 (Box 87, Folder 2722)
    - 1943 (Box 88, Folder 2723)
    - 1960 (Box 88, Folder 2724)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 88, Folder 2725)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 88, Folder 2726 - 2728)
  - Convention, State YMCA, 1930-1931 (Box 88, Folder 2729)
  - Co-op, 1934 (Box 88, Folder 2730)
  - Co-op, 1975 (Box 88, Folder 2731)
  - Cooperative Consumers of New Haven, undated (Box 88, Folder 2732)
  - Cooperative Credit Union
    - 1958-1959 (Box 88, Folder 2733)
    - 1960 (Box 88, Folder 2734)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 88, Folder 2735 - 2736)
  - Cooperatives, 1935-1937 (Box 88, Folder 2737)
  - Coordinated Action Plan for Environmental Education, undated (Box 88, Folder 2738)
  - (Yale) Corporation, 1977 (Box 88, Folder 2739)
  - Correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 88, Folder 2740)
  - Correspondence Regarding Speakers for Churches, 1913-1914 (Box 88, Folder 2741)
  - Correspondence: Summer Project, 1969 (Box 88, Folder 2742)
  - Cosmopolitan Club, 1925-1935 (Box 88, Folder 2743 - 2746)
    - Accounts, 1933-1935 (Box 88, Folder 2747)
  - Council Emphases Recommended at Becket, undated (Box 88, Folder 2748)
  - Council of Christian Associations, 1928-1933 (Box 88, Folder 2749)
  - Council of Churches, 1943 (Box 89, Folder 2750)
  - Council of Churches: New Haven, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 2751)
  - Council of Social Agencies, 1945 (Box 89, Folder 2752)
  - Council of the Yale Christian Community (CYCC)
    - 1955-1957 (Box 89, Folder 2753)
    - 1959 (Box 89, Folder 2754)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 89, Folder 2755)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 89, Folder 2756)
  - Council of World Student Christian Federation (WSCF), 1944 (Box 89, Folder 2757)
  - Council Reports (Doug Miller), 1949 (Box 89, Folder 2758)
  - Courses, Summer School: YUCA, 1913-1921 (Box 89, Folder 2759)
  - Court: Liberal Club, undated (Box 89, Folder 2760)
  - Cousins, 1943 (Box 89, Folder 2761)
  - Criterion
    - 1952 (Box 89, Folder 2762)
    - 1953-1955 (Box 89, Folder 2763)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 89, Folder 2764)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 89, Folder 2765)
    - 1967-1969 (Box 89, Folder 2766)
  - Criterion Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 89, Folder 2767)
  - Criterion Correspondence, 1968 (Box 89, Folder 2768)
  - Criterion Mailing List, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 2769)
  - Culinary Institute, 1955-1956 (Box 89, Folder 2770)